<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">

  <channel>
    <title>estradiol.dog</title>
    <link>http://10.150.0.4:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent blog posts on estradiol.dog</description>
    
    <generator>Hugo (https://gohugo.io)</generator>
    
    <language>en</language>
    
    <managingEditor>maddi@puppygirl.io (Maddi)</managingEditor>
    
    <webMaster>maddi@puppygirl.io (Maddi)</webMaster>
    
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
    <atom:link href="http://10.150.0.4:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    

    <item>
      <title>What got this dog woofing and barking at servers</title>
      <link>http://10.150.0.4:1313/posts/2025/08/firstpost/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <author>maddi@puppygirl.io (Maddi)</author>

      
      
      
      

      <description>
       So you&amp;amp;rsquo;re still confused as to what the purpose of this whole site is. Well let me try to maybe explain it a bit.
Frist, hi! I&amp;amp;rsquo;m Maddi. I am a total nerd when it comes to computers and technology as a whole. I have such an immense fascination with it that I have spent a majority of my life learning as much as I can about how things work.

      </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://10.150.0.4:1313/posts/2025/08/firstpost/first-post/</guid>
    </item>
    

    <item>
      <title>What Is A Therian?</title>
      <link>http://10.150.0.4:1313/posts/2025/08/whatisatherian/what-is-a-therian/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <author>maddi@puppygirl.io (Maddi)</author>

      
      
      
      

      <description>
       # So what is exactly is a &amp;amp;ldquo;Therian&amp;amp;rdquo;? More specifically what is therianthropy? And what is a therianthrope? Well according to the Therian Wiki
The noun/term &amp;amp;rsquo;therianthropy&amp;amp;rsquo; is used to refer to the intrinsic experience surrounding someone&amp;amp;rsquo;s therian identity. It is the term used to encapsulate the broader experience, while the term &amp;amp;rsquo;therianthrope&amp;amp;rsquo; (someone who involuntarily identifies as a non-human animalistic creature) refers to the individual who experiences it.

      </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://10.150.0.4:1313/posts/2025/08/whatisatherian/what-is-a-therian/</guid>
    </item>
    

    <item>
      <title>Sunshine &amp; Moonlight</title>
      <link>http://10.150.0.4:1313/posts/2025/08/sunshineandmoonlight/sunshine-and-moonlight-setting-up-lan-game-streaming-copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <author>maddi@puppygirl.io (Maddi)</author>

      
      
      
      

      <description>
       # awoooooooo # This is what I wrote to nate. Make this a blog post lol My desktop is connected via a 10G fiber link to the core switch. You don&amp;amp;rsquo;t fully need this and honestly could get away with a 1G copper link
You need to ensure that the GPU/CPU can handle encoding video at whatever bitrate you&amp;amp;rsquo;re going to be pushing. In my case I push a full 150Mbps using AV1 (which is experimental btw, I just switched to it because HEVC looked like shit with a lot of artifacting)

      </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://10.150.0.4:1313/posts/2025/08/sunshineandmoonlight/sunshine-and-moonlight-setting-up-lan-game-streaming-copy/</guid>
    </item>
    

    <item>
      <title>Madeleine - Resume</title>
      <link>http://10.150.0.4:1313/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <author>maddi@puppygirl.io (Maddi)</author>

      
      
      
      

      <description>
       # Contact Information Madeleine &amp;amp;ndash; maddi@puppygirl [dot] io | #### Enterprise Infrastructure | System Administration | Networking | Cloud Computing | AI Platform Expert | Home Labber # Skills ### Technical &amp;amp;amp; Data Center Expertise Extensive experience in data center operations, with a proven track record across diverse environments, including compute, storage, and AI. A blend of operational proficiency and strategic implementation, honed at both large corporations and through personal lab projects

      </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://10.150.0.4:1313/resume/</guid>
    </item>
    

    <item>
      <title>Pawsitively Me</title>
      <link>http://10.150.0.4:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <author>maddi@puppygirl.io (Maddi)</author>

      
      
      
      

      <description>
       Hey there!
I&amp;amp;rsquo;m Madeleine but everyone calls me Maddi (It/Its or Pup/Pups)
My hobbies include playing video games, riding my motorcycle or tinkering around with my home lab. For games I usually play shooters or arcade style with friends. I pop in and out of playing MMOs as well. WoW, OSRS and some others
Professionally I am a senior data center technician puppy and work helping to build some of the worlds largest facilities that house the most advanced computing platforms on the planet A little bit about me, I&amp;amp;rsquo;m a transgender female and a furry. I also identify as therian ΘΔ!

      </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://10.150.0.4:1313/about/</guid>
    </item>
    

    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s in my Home Lab</title>
      <link>http://10.150.0.4:1313/home-lab/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <author>maddi@puppygirl.io (Maddi)</author>

      
      
      
      

      <description>
       # My lab! All of the wacky, goofy and insanely over kill equipment and software because I find it fun!
## Before we dive in Something to know, this setup is evolving on a constant basis with new software and hardware. Some of this may be outdated. I will do my best to keep it as close to accurate as possible. Honestly though, if I did, it would probably take a ton of time with every single change. So instead, I&amp;amp;rsquo;m going to try and keep this relatively updated with hardware and roughly with software/services. I also will, at my own discretion, intentionally not mention some details about the configuration for the sake of security.

      </description>
      <guid isPermaLink="true">http://10.150.0.4:1313/home-lab/</guid>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
